I'm gonna say this one time and the next time you see somebody saying to me
don't address these clowns or why do you respond to trolls etc. I want you to let
them know she has a post pinned about this. When I make a video that addresses
some nonsense that someone has said to me it's typically for one of two reasons.
One I'm able to use it as a teaching tool which is then really alchemy because I am
using their negative and turning it into positive literally making it into a gem
or two it is release. It's release. It allows me to send it on. Send in the groove
send it right back to you. Instead of it living inside of me metastasizing or
doing this thing of pretending like it's not within me and then it actually is I
process it into something else. Either way in either example I am doing what's best for me
and I know it seems odd but I actually do know what's best for me. If you do not want to
see that type of content scroll on by but know that the purpose is always of value
whether it's value for you or me or both of us.
Ba dum ba. Support a real one.